{
    "subject": "resource/Ray_(film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/producer",
    "object": "resource/Stuart_Benjamin",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Ray' was produced by Stuart Benjamin.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9572708010673523,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Stuart Benjamin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279440641403198,
            "question": "What is the name of the film produced by Stuart Benjamin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8617753982543945,
            "question": "Is Stuart Benjamin involved in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8129310607910156,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Ray'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.499950647354126,
            "question": "Who was the subject of the film 'Ray'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4062810242176056,
            "question": "What kind of work does Stuart Benjamin do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3423736095428467,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film 'Ray'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11691935360431671,
            "question": "Who are some other producers known for their work in film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11650334298610687,
            "question": "What are some popular films produced by others?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06250405311584473,
            "question": "What are some other biographical films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Ray' was produced by Stuart Benjamin.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2660_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular films produced by others?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2660_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other producers known for their work in film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2660_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the genre of the film 'Ray'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2660_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2660_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that the film \"Ray\" was indeed produced by Stuart Benjamin. The relevant text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2660/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt is:\n\n\"The producing team behind \u201cRay\u201d has set its sights on Broadway, acquiring rights from the Ray Charles Estate and Ray Charles Enterprises.\n\n Stuart Benjamin \u2014 who worked on \u201cRay\u201d for 15 years before it opened last fall \u2014 will again partner with Howard and Karen Baldwin on the project, to be produced by Benjamin Prods.  and Baldwin Entertainment Group.\"\n\nThis text clearly indicates that Stuart Benjamin was a producer of the film \"Ray\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Stuart Benjamin produced the film \"Ray,\" which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}